williamsauction.com 2014-04-08

# Privacy Statement

Williams & Williams Marketing Services, Inc. ("Williams & Williams") respects your privacy. When using our website (the "Williams & Williams Website"), you may get information, access online products and services, communicate with us or link to other websites with which we do business. While doing that, you may give us information so that we can provide enhanced products or services to you and to personalize your experience on the Williams & Williams Website. This online privacy policy describes how we use and protect personally identifiable information that you share with us.

Williams & Williams is the sole owner of the information collected on the Williams & Williams Website. We will not use or disclose this information to others in ways different from what is stated in this Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy may change within our sole discretion from time to time, so please revisit this Privacy Policy from time to time to be sure that you are familiar with the then-current policy.

Please be advised that these principles do not govern websites of other parties to which we may provide only links, as Williams & Williams is not responsible for, and cannot control the privacy practices or content of, those third party websites.

**Information Collection and Use**  
Williams & Williams collects, uses and retains personal information when you register with the Williams & Williams Website, when you use Williams & Williams applications and other services, when you visit Williams & Williams website pages or the pages of certain Williams & Williams partners, and when you enter promotions. Williams & Williams may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register with the Williams & Williams website as a member, we ask for your name and email address, plus, in some cases, physical address, telephone numbers, and similar contact information, credit card information or other financial information when you engage in bidding and/or order services on-line. Moreover, you may be asked to provide additional information such as birth date, gender, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Some of our members may use Williams & Williams applications and other services to participate in private auctions and/or chat forums which will require the participants to register prior to attending the private auction or forum, as well.

Williams & Williams collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of our various Williams & Williams applications and other services. This information may be submitted from: applications or other forms we receive from you or your authorized representative; from your transactions with, or from the services being performed by, us, our affiliates, or others; and from the public records maintained by governmental entities that we either obtain directly from those entities, or from our affiliates, or others; and from consumer or other reporting agencies.

Williams & Williams automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address and Williams & Williams website cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.

Williams & Williams routinely collects information that cannot be identified to a particular individual such as time-stamps and logs events (such as features used, length of viewing, etc.) This data may be used for accounting/billing purposes as well as for performance and optimization of the Williams & Williams applications and other services.

Williams & Williams uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for Applications and other services, improve our applications and other services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure.**  
Williams & Williams does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Williams & Williams under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Williams & Williams communicate with you about offers from Williams & Williams and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We provide information to agents, brokers, or representatives to provide you with services you have requested; to third party contractors or service providers who provide services or perform marketing or other functions on our behalf; and to others with whom we enter into joint marketing agreements for products or services that we believe you may find of interest.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, and reserve the right to disclose any information submitted to provide responses to such legal processes or enforce our rights.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud or counterfeiting, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Williams & Williams Website’s Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if Williams & Williams is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Williams & Williams will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Williams & Williams may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria.

Williams & Williams does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

Williams & Williams website advertisers may include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, software companies, and others).

Williams & Williams may work with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.

**Cookies.**  
Williams & Williams may set and access Williams & Williams website cookies on your computer.

Williams & Williams may let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Williams & Williams’s cookies.

Williams & Williams may use web beacons to access Williams & Williams website cookies inside and outside our network of websites and in connection with Williams & Williams applications and other services.

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Membership Information and Preferences.  
You can edit your Williams & Williams website membership information at any time.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to Williams & Williams website applications and other services, such as new application or service announcements, administrative messages and newsletters that are considered part of your Williams & Williams website membership, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

You can terminate your Williams & Williams website membership at any time.

**Confidentiality and Security.**  
We limit access to personal information about you to employees, agents and representatives who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide Applications and other services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

Further, the only means to participate in an auction is through the Williams & Williams website registration and access process, which should include a password for each transmission. Williams & Williams strongly recommends that all private transmissions be protected by passwords.

**Privacy Contact**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or about our information-collection practices, please contact us at legal@williamsauction.com Alternatively, you can contact us at Williams & Williams Marketing Services, Inc., 7120 South Lewis, Suite 200, Tulsa, Oklahoma 74136, USA.

Copyright 2011 Williams & Williams Marketing Services, Inc. * All rights reserved

Use of this website constitutes acceptance of the Williams & Williams’ Terms of Use and Privacy Policy

History 

OKroots 

Team Bios 

In the News 

Partners 

Contact Us 

Organizations 

Careers 

Enter your E-mail Address 

or Edit My Auction Alerts

**Please enter an e-mail address.**  
If you are already signed up to receive auction alerts and would like to edit  
your preferences
